http://www.allmypapers.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
All My Papers is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. In accordance with the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, this page details how we deal with any information collected through this site.
The All My Papers site uses cookies to customize your viewing experience (for example, if you have been to our site before, we endeavor to not repeatedly display the “Latest News” popup dialog.  All My Papers uses web analytics services provided by LeadLander (LeadLander Privacy Policy) which uses JavaScript and cookies to help us analyze how visitors use our website. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. If cookies are refused, you will still be able to use our website but anonymous data will still be collected.
We collect personal information about you only when you elect to provide such information to us, such as when you register to receive product and services information, request additional information from us, or submit an email to us. The information collected might include your name, company name, title, email address, phone number, fax number, etc. Any personal information collected will be used solely for the purpose(s) for which it was collected, unless you indicate otherwise. The personal information you provide to us will not be sold or shared with third parties or outside vendors.
Please note that All My Papers Software is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other web sites to which this site may link.
Contact All My Papers Contact All My Papers to automate check Image Cash Letter (ICL) file processing.
Click Here
